Dreams of when
humanity will take
that first Starship
to Mars.
Through the dark
and endless night
We're chasing dreams,
we're taking flight
Past the moon,
beyond the sky
A world unknown
where hopes
will thrive
The engines hum,
the stars align
A million miles
of space
and time
Leave behind the
earthbound scars
We're on a
starship to Mars
On a starship
to Mars
We're breaking
the chains
Through cosmic winds
we ride
the flames
A crimson horizon,
a brave
new start
On a starship
to Mars,
we follow
our hearts
Dusty plains and
skies of red
A planet
untouched, unsaid
In the
silence, dreams ignite
A frontier born
in the
Martian light
Through the void
we make
our way
Carving paths
where stars
don't stray
A colony of
shining stars
Begins on the
sands of Mars
On a starship
to Mars
We're breaking
the chains
Through cosmic winds
we ride
the flames
A crimson horizon,
a brave
new start
On a starship
to Mars, we
follow our hearts
So here we
stand, where
dreams collide
On Martian soil,
our hope,
our guide
Earth's echoes are
faint and far
But we shine
like a
morning star
Through this starship
to Mars
Build a future
for you
and me
Through the cosmos
across the stars
We've found our
home on Mars
On a starship
to Mars
We're breaking
the chains
Through cosmic winds
we ride
the flames
A crimson horizon,
a brave
new start
On a starship
to Mars
A starship
We follow
our hearts